It's cocktail time!
It's a Friday night and it's cocktail time.
Obviously.
I got this stuff. It's called craft mix.
It leads a bunch of packets of drinks.
So this is a poulema, margarita.
There's a bunch of other ones in here.
We're going to try this and see how it tastes.
Basically, you need to pour it in the packets
and then you add water and sparkling water.
Sparkling water, but we're not going to shake it
because last time that did not go so well.
Refer to cocktail time number one.
Do you add in your alcohol choice?
We're going to be doing tequila today
because we are tequila girls.
Like, foaming amosa.
I don't think...
I think we're going to do one shot of tequila.
We put some ice in it.
Now we're mixing it up.
Cheers to yours.
Wait, that's like really bad.
It's not bad.
It's like a K-point 2.
I think that we're really bad bartenders besides you.
Yeah, Amy is actually a bartender.
I'm not even doing this.
I don't know. I can't taste the tequila at all.
And it's 25 calories per packet.
Like, that's actually so good.
Did you hear that?
25!
I was like, I give this like a nine.
This is like so quick and easy and I love it.
Yeah, I picked nine.
Cheers!